{
    "subject": "resource/Republic_of_Texas",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Washington-on-the-Brazos,_Texas",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Republic of Texas is Washington-on-the-Brazos, Texas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9734805822372437,
            "question": "Was the capital of the Republic of Texas called something else before Washington-on-the-Brazos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9428346157073975,
            "question": "Is Washington-on-the-Brazos in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9322136044502258,
            "question": "Why do you think Washington-on-the-Brazos was chosen as the capital of the Republic of Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8863681554794312,
            "question": "What country had Washington-on-the-Brazos as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.883146345615387,
            "question": "What is the capital of the Republic of Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8657684326171875,
            "question": "Where was the capital of the Republic of Texas located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8628387451171875,
            "question": "During what period was Washington-on-the-Brazos the capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8214729428291321,
            "question": "What was the name of the capital city of the Republic of Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8082458972930908,
            "question": "What is significant about Washington-on-the-Brazos in Texas history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6285518407821655,
            "question": "Can you name any historical events that took place in Washington-on-the-Brazos?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Republic of Texas is Washington-on-the-Brazos, Texas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9283_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is significant about Washington-on-the-Brazos in Texas history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9283_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the capital city of the Republic of Texas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9283_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During what period was Washington-on-the-Brazos the capital?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9283_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9283_41.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents describe Washington-on-the-Brazos as the first capital of the Republic of Texas (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9283/re-ranker-msmarco/29.txt) and later confirm that it was also the second capital, after Harrisburg on Buffalo Bayou was used as a temporary capital (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9283/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt). Additionally, one of the documents states that Washington-on-the-Brazos served as the last capital of the Republic of Texas from 1842-1845 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9283/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt). Therefore, based on the information provided in the documents, it is correct that Washington-on-the-Brazos was a capital of the Republic of Texas."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided documents, Washington-on-the-Brazos was not the capital of the Republic of Texas for an extended period. It served as the first capital and also briefly as the second capital from 1842-1845. However, after the United States annexed Texas in 1846, Austin replaced Washington-on-the-Brazos as the capital of the Lone Star State."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context states that while Washington-on-the-Brazos was the first capital of the Republic of Texas, it served as such for only a brief period from March 1, 1836, until March 1842. After this, the capital moved to Harrisburg and then to nearer-to-Austin locations before Austin became the permanent capital in 1846.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}